ausgamers.com 2016-11-23

# AusGamers Privacy Policy - AusGamers.com

### AusGamers Pty Ltd

## General

AusGamers Pty Ltd ('AusGamers') is committed to protecting the personal information it collects from you. However, AusGamers is not required to comply with the provisions of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and while not purporting to be a statement of compliance with that Act, this document sets out how AusGamers will manage your personal information.

## Collection

AusGamers may collect and hold personal information about you, including your name, gender, address, phone number, email address, bank account details, credit card details or other information relevant to providing you with the services you are seeking.

The personal information that AusGamers collects and holds about you, depends on your interaction with AusGamers. Generally, AusGamers will collect and hold your personal information for the purpose of:

  * providing AusGamers's services to you; 
  * providing you with information about other services that AusGamers offers that may be of interest to you; 
  * facilitating AusGamers's internal business operations, including the fulfilment of any legal requirements; and 
  * analysing AusGamers's services and customer needs with a view to developing new or improved services. 

Personal information will generally be collected by AusGamers directly from you through standard application and registration forms or your other interactions with AusGamers. There may, however, be some instances where personal information about you will be collected indirectly because it is unreasonable or impractical to collect personal information directly from you. We will usually notify you about these instances in advance, or where that is not possible, as soon as reasonably practicable after the information has been collected.

If you access AusGamers's web site, AusGamers may collect additional personal information about you in the form of your IP address (that is, the single numerical address for your computer on the internet, which consists of four consecutive numbers ranging between 0 and 255) or domain name (that is, the textual address for your location on the internet which corresponds to your IP address, which the internet computers can read).

Also, AusGamers's web site uses cookies. A cookie is a message given by a web server (that is, a computer that delivers or serves up pages on the world wide web such as www.AusGamers.com.au) to a web browser (that is, software, such as Microsoft Internet Explorer, used to locate and display pages on the world wide web). The web browser stores the message in a text file. The message is then sent back to the web server each time the web browser requests a page from the web server.

The main purpose of cookies is to identify users and to prepare customised web pages for them. When you enter a web site using cookies, you may be asked to fill out a form providing such information as your name and interests. This information is packaged into a cookie and sent to your web browser, which stores it for later use. The next time you go to the same web site, your web browser will send the cookie to the web server. The web server can then use this information to present you with customised web pages. So, for example, instead of seeing just a generic welcome page, you might see a welcome page with your name on it.

Cookies do not identify you personally, but they may link back to a database record about you. If you register on AusGamers's web site, AusGamers will then link your cookie back to your personal information details.

AusGamers uses cookies to monitor usage of AusGamers's web site and to create a personal record of when you visit AusGamers's web site and what pages you view so that AusGamers may serve you more effectively.

If the personal information you provide to AusGamers is incomplete or inaccurate, AusGamers may be unable to administer your investments smoothly or provide you with the services you are seeking.

## Use and disclosure

Generally, AusGamers only uses or discloses personal information about you for the purposes for which it was collected (as set out above). However, AusGamers may also disclose personal information about you to:

  * financial institutions, who process any payments you make to AusGamers; and 
  * service providers, who assist AusGamers in operating its business, however, these service providers are required to comply with AusGamers's privacy policy in how they handle your personal information. 

## Security

AusGamers may store your personal information in different ways, including in paper and in electronic form. The security of your personal information is important to AusGamers. AusGamers takes all reasonable measures to ensure that your personal information is stored safely to protect it from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure, including electronic and physical security measures.

## Access

You may access personal information AusGamers holds about you, upon making a written request. AusGamers will endeavour to acknowledge your request within 14 days of its receipt and to provide you with access to the information requested within 30 days. AusGamers may charge you a reasonable fee for processing your request. 

AusGamers may decline a request for access to personal information in the limited circumstances permitted by the Privacy Act.

If, upon receiving access to your personal information or at any other time, you believe the personal information AusGamers holds about you is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date, please notify AusGamers immediately. AusGamers will take reasonable steps to correct the information so that it is accurate, complete and up to date. If AusGamers disagrees with you about whether your personal information is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date, and you ask AusGamers to associate with your personal information a statement claiming that your personal information is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date, AusGamers will take reasonable steps to do so.

## Links to other web sites

AusGamers's web site may contain links to other web sites. AusGamers is not responsible for the privacy practices of linked web sites and so linked web sites are not subject to AusGamers's privacy policies and proceay in which AusGamers handles your personal information, please contact AusGamers's privacy officer at: 

Street address: Suite S04/34 Coonan Street, Indooroopilly, Queensland,Australia, 4068   
Postal address: Suite S04/34 Coonan Street, Indooroopilly, Queensland,Australia, 4068   
Email address: contact AT ausgamers [dot] com   
Telephone: +61-7-3721-5000   
Facsimile: +61-7-3721-5001 

## More information

For more information about privacy in general, you can visit the Federal Privacy Commissioner's web site at [http://www.privacy.gov.au](http://www.privacy.gov.au/).

## Advertising

Cookies are used by Third Party vendors to serve ads on our website, including Google AdSense and DoubleClick.   
You can opt out interest-based ads served from Google by visiting [http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).
